#### Contact

amberhorde@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amber-rose-horde-1555047b (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Cpr Certified

Nursing

Clinical Research

## Amber-Rose Horde

Case Manager at Medical Solutions

Houston, Texas Area

#### Summary

I am a young, inspired nursing professional with over 5 years of experience in the critical care, emergency room and post anesthesia care environment as well as almost 2 years as an RN Case Manager. As an RN III and Case Manager, I have aspirations of developing innovative ways to coordinate evidence based practices with the art and science of nursing to increase patient safety and quality of care.

With many talents, I am a proud member of Delta Sigma Theta Sorority, Inc., and CEO of Amber Rose Consulting. My mission is to increase successful young business professionals in the city of Houston by striving to teach networking strategies, providing workshops and classes, as well as, expose the community to elite social events to enhance their entrepreneurial knowledge when creating and growing a business. With over six years of experience in business development, I started this journey taking business classes and attending business development seminars hosted by the Houston Black Chamber of Commerce and Texas Young Professionals Organization. I have started and organized businesses such as independently owned sports facilities, Real Estate, Small Boutiques, Hair Salons, and Day Cares.

### Experience

Medical Solutions
Case Manager
August 2019 - Present (1 year)
Travel

My role as a Travel Case Manager is a collaborative process of assessment, planning, care coordination, and advocacy for options and services to meet the patient's comprehensive health needs. Through effective communication and available resources I promote patient safety and quality of care while taking into consideration patient and hospital costs.

## Amber Rose Consulting

CEO

November 2015 - Present (4 years 9 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Amber Rose Consulting is here for all young professionals in the Greater Houston area. We will offer classes, workshops and networking events for you to get acclimated to Corporate America as well as help young professionals create their own businesses.

Midtown Surgical Specialists, PC Registered Nurse December 2017 - November 2019 (2 years)

Houston, Texas Area

Pre-Op/PACU

- Monitor and ensure stability of patient's vital signs and administere medication when appropriate.
- Recognize clinical abnormalities then communicate with anesthesiologist in reference to diagnosing and treating of clinical problems.
- Manage patient care analgesia for pain management.
- Educate and support patient and family on care of patient

#### CHI St. Luke's Patients Medical Center Case Manager April 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 5 months)

Pasadena, Texas

Ensure that patients are admitted and transitioned to the appropriate level of care, have an effective plan of care and are receiving prescribed treatment, and have an advocate for services and plans needed during and after their stay.

# Houston Methodist Sugar Land RN II

July 2016 - February 2018 (1 year 8 months)

Sugar Land, Texas

- Conduct and present Evidence Based Practice Research.
- Accurately gather information in a systematic manner in order to determine health-related needs.
- Give compassionate care to critical patients suffering from injuries or debilitating conditions.

• Manage life support equipment and IV administration fluids and medications.

#### Committees:

- Clinical Practice Council Committee
- Employee Satisfaction Committee
- Patient Satisfaction Committee
- Nursing Engagement Committee

Houston Methodist St. John Hospital Registered Nurse January 2015 - July 2016 (1 year 7 months)

- Educate patient and patient families about medications, conditions and provided support as needed.
- Assist physicians with a broad scope of clinical procedures utilizing various invasive / non-invasive monitoring equipment.
- Monitor telemetry and respond to codes and rapid responses.
- Examines data to grasp issues, draw conclusions, and solve problems.

#### Committees:

- Clinical Practice Council Committee
- Employee Satisfaction Committee
- Patient Satisfaction Committee
- Code Blue Committee

#### Education

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Master's degree, Nursing · (2016 - 2018)

Sam Houston State University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Nursing · (2009 - 2014)